let data = [
  {
    question: "Who was named the 2021 NBA Finals MVP?",
    answers: [
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
      "LeBron James",
      "Kevin Durant",
      "Stephen Curry",
    ],
    correct: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team holds the record for the longest winning streak in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Chicago Bulls",
    ],
    correct: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player won the NBA scoring title in the 2018-2019 season?",
    answers: [
      "Stephen Curry",
      "James Harden",
      "Kawhi Leonard",
      "Damian Lillard",
    ],
    correct: "James Harden",
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first overall pick in the 2012 NBA Draft?",
    answers: [
      "Anthony Davis",
      "Kyrie Irving",
      "Karl-Anthony Towns",
      "Andrew Wiggins",
    ],
    correct: "Anthony Davis",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA player has the nickname 'The Process'?",
    answers: [
      "Joel Embiid",
      "Ben Simmons",
      "Karl-Anthony Towns",
      "Anthony Davis",
    ],
    correct: "Joel Embiid",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team drafted Dirk Nowitzki in the 1998 NBA Draft?",
    answers: [
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Phoenix Suns",
      "Sacramento Kings",
    ],
    correct: "Milwaukee Bucks",
  },
  {
    question: "Who holds the NBA record for most assists in a single game?",
    answers: ["Magic Johnson", "John Stockton", "Scott Skiles", "Jason Kidd"],
    correct: "Scott Skiles",
  },
  {
    question: "Which coach has the most NBA championships?",
    answers: ["Phil Jackson", "Pat Riley", "Red Auerbach", "Gregg Popovich"],
    correct: "Phil Jackson",
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the 2019 NBA MVP?",
    answers: [
      "James Harden",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
      "LeBron James",
      "Kawhi Leonard",
    ],
    correct: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team won the NBA championship in the 2010-2011 season?",
    answers: [
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
    ],
    correct: "Dallas Mavericks",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was named NBA Rookie of the Year in 2018?",
    answers: ["Donovan Mitchell", "Jayson Tatum", "Ben Simmons", "Luka Dončić"],
    correct: "Ben Simmons",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team won the most NBA championships in the 1990s?",
    answers: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Houston Rockets",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
    ],
    correct: "Chicago Bulls",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most three-pointers made in NBA history?",
    answers: ["Stephen Curry", "Ray Allen", "Reggie Miller", "Klay Thompson"],
    correct: "Stephen Curry",
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the 2013 NBA Finals MVP?",
    answers: ["LeBron James", "Kawhi Leonard", "Dwyane Wade", "Kevin Durant"],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player was traded for Chris Paul in the 2011 trade between the Clippers and Hornets?",
    answers: [
      "Eric Gordon",
      "Blake Griffin",
      "Paul George",
      "Russell Westbrook",
    ],
    correct: "Eric Gordon",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player won the NBA Most Improved Player award in 2017?",
    answers: [
      "Victor Oladipo",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
      "Pascal Siakam",
      "CJ McCollum",
    ],
    correct: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player scored 70 points in a game for the Phoenix Suns in 2017?",
    answers: ["Devin Booker", "Kevin Durant", "James Harden", "Klay Thompson"],
    correct: "Devin Booker",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team was Kevin Garnett traded to in 2007?",
    answers: [
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Brooklyn Nets",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Chicago Bulls",
    ],
    correct: "Boston Celtics",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA player was nicknamed 'The Mailman'?",
    answers: [
      "Karl Malone",
      "Charles Barkley",
      "Patrick Ewing",
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
    ],
    correct: "Karl Malone",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player won the 2014 NBA MVP award?",
    answers: ["LeBron James", "Kevin Durant", "Stephen Curry", "James Harden"],
    correct: "Kevin Durant",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team drafted Luka Dončić in the 2018 NBA Draft?",
    answers: [
      "Atlanta Hawks",
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "Phoenix Suns",
      "Sacramento Kings",
    ],
    correct: "Atlanta Hawks",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player led the NBA in assists in the 2020-2021 season?",
    answers: ["Chris Paul", "Russell Westbrook", "James Harden", "Trae Young"],
    correct: "Russell Westbrook",
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the NBA Sixth Man of the Year award in 2019?",
    answers: [
      "Lou Williams",
      "Montrezl Harrell",
      "Eric Gordon",
      "Dennis Schröder",
    ],
    correct: "Lou Williams",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team won the NBA championship in 2004?",
    answers: [
      "Detroit Pistons",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Miami Heat",
    ],
    correct: "Detroit Pistons",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most blocks in a single NBA game?",
    answers: [
      "Dikembe Mutombo",
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      "Elmore Smith",
      "Manute Bol",
    ],
    correct: "Elmore Smith",
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the NBA Defensive Player of the Year award in 2020?",
    answers: [
      "Rudy Gobert",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
      "Anthony Davis",
      "Kawhi Leonard",
    ],
    correct: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was the 2017 NBA Finals MVP?",
    answers: ["Kevin Durant", "LeBron James", "Stephen Curry", "Klay Thompson"],
    correct: "Kevin Durant",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team did Shaquille O'Neal play for after leaving the Los Angeles Lakers?",
    answers: [
      "Miami Heat",
      "Phoenix Suns",
      "Cleveland Cavaliers",
      "Orlando Magic",
    ],
    correct: "Miami Heat",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the all-time leading scorer in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "LeBron James",
      "Karl Malone",
      "Michael Jordan",
    ],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player won the 2016 NBA Finals MVP?",
    answers: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Kyrie Irving",
      "Draymond Green",
      "Stephen Curry",
    ],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA team did Wilt Chamberlain play for when he scored 100 points in a game?",
    answers: [
      "Philadelphia Warriors",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "San Francisco Warriors",
      "New York Knicks",
    ],
    correct: "Philadelphia Warriors",
  },
  {
    question: "Who holds the record for the most NBA MVP awards?",
    answers: [
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "LeBron James",
      "Bill Russell",
    ],
    correct: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the first player to win NBA MVP, Defensive Player of the Year, and Finals MVP in the same season?",
    answers: [
      "Michael Jordan",
      "LeBron James",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
    ],
    correct: "Michael Jordan",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player is known for his 'Sky Hook' shot?",
    answers: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      "Bill Russell",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
    ],
    correct: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team did Kobe Bryant play his entire NBA career for?",
    answers: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Phoenix Suns",
      "Charlotte Hornets",
      "Chicago Bulls",
    ],
    correct: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team won the 2008 NBA championship?",
    answers: [
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Detroit Pistons",
    ],
    correct: "Boston Celtics",
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first player to be unanimously voted NBA MVP?",
    answers: [
      "Stephen Curry",
      "LeBron James",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Magic Johnson",
    ],
    correct: "Stephen Curry",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player won the NBA Slam Dunk Contest in 2000?",
    answers: ["Vince Carter", "Kobe Bryant", "Dwight Howard", "Blake Griffin"],
    correct: "Vince Carter",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team drafted Anthony Davis as the first overall pick?",
    answers: [
      "New Orleans Hornets",
      "Cleveland Cavaliers",
      "Charlotte Bobcats",
      "Washington Wizards",
    ],
    correct: "New Orleans Hornets",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team won the NBA championship in 1999?",
    answers: [
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "New York Knicks",
    ],
    correct: "San Antonio Spurs",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most points scored in a single NBA game?",
    answers: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "David Robinson",
      "Michael Jordan",
    ],
    correct: "Wilt Chamberlain",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team did Kareem Abdul-Jabbar play for before joining the Los Angeles Lakers?",
    answers: [
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "New York Knicks",
      "Boston Celtics",
    ],
    correct: "Milwaukee Bucks",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player was the youngest to score 30,000 career points in the NBA?",
    answers: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Kobe Bryant",
    ],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team did Dennis Rodman play for immediately after leaving the Chicago Bulls?",
    answers: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "Detroit Pistons",
    ],
    correct: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the first player in NBA history to record a quadruple-double?",
    answers: [
      "Nate Thurmond",
      "David Robinson",
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      "Alvin Robertson",
    ],
    correct: "Nate Thurmond",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most blocked shots in a single NBA season?",
    answers: ["Mark Eaton", "Hakeem Olajuwon", "Dikembe Mutombo", "Manute Bol"],
    correct: "Mark Eaton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player scored the most points in a single NBA Finals game?",
    answers: ["Elgin Baylor", "Jerry West", "LeBron James", "Shaquille O'Neal"],
    correct: "Elgin Baylor",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most career triple-doubles in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "Russell Westbrook",
      "Oscar Robertson",
      "Magic Johnson",
      "Jason Kidd",
    ],
    correct: "Russell Westbrook",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team drafted Dirk Nowitzki in the 1998 NBA Draft?",
    answers: [
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "Phoenix Suns",
      "Golden State Warriors",
    ],
    correct: "Milwaukee Bucks",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA coach has the most career wins?",
    answers: ["Don Nelson", "Gregg Popovich", "Lenny Wilkens", "Phil Jackson"],
    correct: "Don Nelson",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player holds the record for most steals in an NBA game?",
    answers: ["Kendall Gill", "Larry Kenon", "Allen Iverson", "Chris Paul"],
    correct: "Larry Kenon",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player won the first NBA Defensive Player of the Year award?",
    answers: [
      "Sidney Moncrief",
      "Michael Cooper",
      "Dennis Johnson",
      "Mark Eaton",
    ],
    correct: "Sidney Moncrief",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player was the first to achieve 50-40-90 shooting splits for a season?",
    answers: ["Larry Bird", "Steve Nash", "Mark Price", "Kevin Durant"],
    correct: "Larry Bird",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most assists in a single NBA game?",
    answers: ["Scott Skiles", "John Stockton", "Magic Johnson", "Jason Kidd"],
    correct: "Scott Skiles",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the only player to win the NBA MVP award as a rookie?",
    answers: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Magic Johnson",
      "Oscar Robertson",
      "Wes Unseld",
    ],
    correct: "Wes Unseld",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player was the first to score 2000 points in a single season?",
    answers: ["George Mikan", "Bob Pettit", "Paul Arizin", "Joe Fulks"],
    correct: "George Mikan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team holds the record for the longest winning streak in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Houston Rockets",
    ],
    correct: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was the first to reach 10,000 career assists?",
    answers: [
      "Magic Johnson",
      "John Stockton",
      "Isiah Thomas",
      "Oscar Robertson",
    ],
    correct: "John Stockton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most career rebounds in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Bill Russell",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Moses Malone",
    ],
    correct: "Wilt Chamberlain",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most three-pointers made in a single NBA season?",
    answers: ["Stephen Curry", "Ray Allen", "James Harden", "Klay Thompson"],
    correct: "Stephen Curry",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was known as 'The Big O'?",
    answers: ["Oscar Robertson", "Olajuwon", "O'Neal", "Olson"],
    correct: "Oscar Robertson",
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first non-American player to be named NBA MVP?",
    answers: ["Hakeem Olajuwon", "Dirk Nowitzki", "Tim Duncan", "Steve Nash"],
    correct: "Hakeem Olajuwon",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most career playoff points?",
    answers: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Kobe Bryant",
    ],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team has the most NBA championships?",
    answers: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
    ],
    correct: "Boston Celtics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player was the first to be drafted directly out of high school?",
    answers: ["Moses Malone", "Kevin Garnett", "Kobe Bryant", "Darryl Dawkins"],
    correct: "Darryl Dawkins",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player won the most NBA MVP awards?",
    answers: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Bill Russell",
      "LeBron James",
    ],
    correct: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player has the highest career points-per-game average in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "LeBron James",
      "Kobe Bryant",
    ],
    correct: "Michael Jordan",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most assists in NBA playoff history?",
    answers: ["Magic Johnson", "John Stockton", "LeBron James", "Jason Kidd"],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most career triple-doubles in the NBA Finals?",
    answers: ["Magic Johnson", "LeBron James", "Larry Bird", "Tim Duncan"],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for the highest career free throw percentage?",
    answers: ["Steve Nash", "Mark Price", "Steph Curry", "Rick Barry"],
    correct: "Steve Nash",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team holds the record for most wins in a single regular season?",
    answers: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
    ],
    correct: "Golden State Warriors",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was the first to be unanimously voted NBA MVP?",
    answers: [
      "Stephen Curry",
      "LeBron James",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Michael Jordan",
    ],
    correct: "Stephen Curry",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player scored the most points in an NBA All-Star Game?",
    answers: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Anthony Davis",
      "Russell Westbrook",
    ],
    correct: "Anthony Davis",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most rebounds in a single NBA game?",
    answers: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Bill Russell",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Elvin Hayes",
    ],
    correct: "Wilt Chamberlain",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most blocked shots in NBA playoff history?",
    answers: [
      "Tim Duncan",
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "David Robinson",
    ],
    correct: "Tim Duncan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team was the first to go undefeated in an entire NBA playoff run?",
    answers: [
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
    ],
    correct: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was known as 'The Iceman'?",
    answers: [
      "George Gervin",
      "Julius Erving",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Clyde Drexler",
    ],
    correct: "George Gervin",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player was the first to average a triple-double for an entire season?",
    answers: [
      "Oscar Robertson",
      "Russell Westbrook",
      "Magic Johnson",
      "James Harden",
    ],
    correct: "Oscar Robertson",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team drafted Kobe Bryant in the 1996 NBA Draft?",
    answers: [
      "Charlotte Hornets",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Philadelphia 76ers",
      "Boston Celtics",
    ],
    correct: "Charlotte Hornets",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most career assists in the NBA Finals?",
    answers: ["Magic Johnson", "LeBron James", "John Stockton", "Isiah Thomas"],
    correct: "Magic Johnson",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most career steals in NBA history?",
    answers: ["John Stockton", "Michael Jordan", "Jason Kidd", "Gary Payton"],
    correct: "John Stockton",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player scored the most points in a single NBA season?",
    answers: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "LeBron James",
    ],
    correct: "Wilt Chamberlain",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player was the first to win the NBA Slam Dunk Contest twice?",
    answers: [
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Dominique Wilkins",
      "Spud Webb",
      "Vince Carter",
    ],
    correct: "Michael Jordan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most free throws made in a single NBA game?",
    answers: [
      "Adrian Dantley",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Karl Malone",
      "James Harden",
    ],
    correct: "Adrian Dantley",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most career 50-point games in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "James Harden",
    ],
    correct: "Wilt Chamberlain",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was the first to achieve 30,000 career points?",
    answers: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Karl Malone",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Julius Erving",
    ],
    correct: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most consecutive games with a triple-double?",
    answers: [
      "Russell Westbrook",
      "Oscar Robertson",
      "James Harden",
      "LeBron James",
    ],
    correct: "Russell Westbrook",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was known as 'The Admiral'?",
    answers: [
      "David Robinson",
      "Patrick Ewing",
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      "Dikembe Mutombo",
    ],
    correct: "David Robinson",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for the most career points in the NBA All-Star Game?",
    answers: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    ],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player won the most NBA championships as a player?",
    answers: ["Bill Russell", "Sam Jones", "John Havlicek", "Robert Horry"],
    correct: "Bill Russell",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most three-pointers made in a single NBA game?",
    answers: [
      "Klay Thompson",
      "Stephen Curry",
      "James Harden",
      "Damian Lillard",
    ],
    correct: "Klay Thompson",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most career minutes played in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "LeBron James",
      "Karl Malone",
      "John Stockton",
    ],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player was the first to win the NBA MVP award three consecutive times?",
    answers: [
      "Larry Bird",
      "Magic Johnson",
      "Bill Russell",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
    ],
    correct: "Larry Bird",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player scored the most points in a single NBA Playoff game?",
    answers: [
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Elgin Baylor",
      "Allen Iverson",
    ],
    correct: "Michael Jordan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player has the highest career field goal percentage in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "DeAndre Jordan",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Artis Gilmore",
    ],
    correct: "DeAndre Jordan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most three-pointers made in a single NBA Finals game?",
    answers: ["Stephen Curry", "Ray Allen", "Klay Thompson", "Danny Green"],
    correct: "Stephen Curry",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most NBA MVP awards?",
    answers: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "LeBron James",
      "Bill Russell",
    ],
    correct: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most career double-doubles in the NBA?",
    answers: ["Tim Duncan", "John Stockton", "Karl Malone", "Wilt Chamberlain"],
    correct: "Tim Duncan",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most career blocked shots in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      "Dikembe Mutombo",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Mark Eaton",
    ],
    correct: "Hakeem Olajuwon",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player was the first to win the NBA Most Improved Player award?",
    answers: [
      "Alvin Robertson",
      "Kevin Duckworth",
      "Tracy McGrady",
      "Gheorghe Muresan",
    ],
    correct: "Alvin Robertson",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for the most career three-point field goals made in NBA history?",
    answers: ["Ray Allen", "Stephen Curry", "Reggie Miller", "James Harden"],
    correct: "Stephen Curry",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player scored the most points in a single quarter of an NBA game?",
    answers: [
      "Klay Thompson",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "David Thompson",
    ],
    correct: "Klay Thompson",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for the most career turnovers in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Karl Malone",
      "John Stockton",
      "Russell Westbrook",
    ],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player was the first to win the NBA Sixth Man of the Year award?",
    answers: [
      "Bobby Jones",
      "Kevin McHale",
      "Detlef Schrempf",
      "Clifford Robinson",
    ],
    correct: "Bobby Jones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most career points in the NBA All-Star Game?",
    answers: ["LeBron James", "Michael Jordan", "Kobe Bryant", "Karl Malone"],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for the highest career free throw percentage?",
    answers: ["Steve Nash", "Steph Curry", "Ray Allen", "Mark Price"],
    correct: "Steph Curry",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team was the first to win an NBA championship after being down 3-1 in the Finals?",
    answers: [
      "Cleveland Cavaliers",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Miami Heat",
    ],
    correct: "Cleveland Cavaliers",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most career field goals made in NBA history?",
    answers: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Karl Malone",
      "LeBron James",
      "Michael Jordan",
    ],
    correct: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for most career rebounds in a single NBA Finals game?",
    answers: [
      "Bill Russell",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Elvin Hayes",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    ],
    correct: "Bill Russell",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player has the highest career free throw percentage in the NBA playoffs?",
    answers: ["Rick Barry", "Ray Allen", "Stephen Curry", "Mark Price"],
    correct: "Rick Barry",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player scored the most points in a single NBA Playoff game?",
    answers: [
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Elgin Baylor",
      "Allen Iverson",
    ],
    correct: "Elgin Baylor",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most career NBA Finals MVP awards?",
    answers: [
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Magic Johnson",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Tim Duncan",
    ],
    correct: "Michael Jordan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player has the highest career free throw percentage in NBA history?",
    answers: ["Steve Nash", "Steph Curry", "Ray Allen", "Mark Price"],
    correct: "Steph Curry",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most career assists in the NBA playoffs?",
    answers: ["Magic Johnson", "John Stockton", "LeBron James", "Jason Kidd"],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
];
